Ahmet Kilinc

Web Developer

Goal-oriented Web Developer brings strong commitment to collaboration and solutions-oriented problem-solving. Use various web design packages to develop custom-crafted, customer-focused websites and designs. Committed to high standards of user experience, usability and speed over more than 5 years for multiple users.

Work History

12-2019 -09-2020

Customer Assistant

Tesco Pls., Clapham, London

- Helped customers complete purchases, locate items and join reward programs to promote loyalty, satisfaction and sales numbers.
- Created balanced pallets to support efficient and safe sales floor replenishment.
- Rotated stock correctly to prevent out-of-date products and removed ageing items from main shelving to build special promotional displays.
- Regularly assessed sales floor stock levels to replenish with back-stock merchandise before depletion.
- Stayed current on available products, store promotions and customer service policies to better shoppers.

07-2018 -09-2018

Junior Web Developer

Absowebly Ltd., Surrey, London

- Designed, developed and implemented software applications for website based on analysed requirements and understanding of industry technical standards.
- Designed and updated layouts to meet usability and performance requirements.
- Adhered to internal risk control and liability mitigation guidelines.
- Pinpointed user experience issues to devise targeted suggestions for creating cohesive user experience.
- Produced websites compatible with multiple browsers.

08-2017 -02-2018

Sales Advisor

Stormfront Apple Premium Reseller, Wimbledon, London

- Listened to customer details and offered matching solutions to meet wide range of requirements.
- Maintained current knowledge of applicable sales and product changes in order to provide best possible service for all customer needs.
- Demonstrated features, answered questions and offered solutions.
- Identified client needs, built relationships and overcame objections to drive sales.
- Completed troubleshooting of malfunctions and diagnosed issues on customers' devices.
- Organised racks and shelves to maintain store visual appeal, engage customers and promote specific merchandise.

12-2016 -08-2017

Sales Advisor

Maplin Electronics, Kingston, London

Contact

Address

Clapham, London

Phone

Available on request.

Email

ahmetskilinc@icloud.com

Website

ahmetk.dev

Education

Bachelor of Science: Computer Science And Programming

Kingston University London, London, United Kingdom

Skills

- Customer Service
- Communication
- Teamwork
- Front End Web Development
 - HTML, CSS, JS
 - PHP
 - React
 - Angular
 - Node
 - NPM
- Bilingual (English & Turkish)
- Leadership
- Overcoming Obstacles
- Adaptability